But you had a conversation with 50,
でも50と話したことあるんだろ
and I heard you say you speak to him
あいつと話したって聞いたぜ
after you got shot before, right?
前に撃たれた後にさ そうだろ？
Yeah.
ああ
He's the perfect example of that, because he had the same thing.
まさにそのいい例だよな
あいつも同じ状況だったから
He couldn't, any way he moved, it was on his ass.
どこへ動こうが
ずっと付け狙われてた
And he had to move militant in a way where it protected him.
だから身を守るために
軍隊みたいに動くしかなかった
How would those conversations have happened or worked?
その話ってどんな感じで
どう進んだの？
With 50 Cent?
50セントと？
Yeah. You know, I just,
うん
なんていうか
I feel like me and 50 Cent is a little different, though.
俺と50セントって
ちょっと違うと思うんだよね
You feel me? And it's crazy, though,
わかる？
でもウケるのがさ
because I did that little old 50 Cent Many Men remix.
俺、50セントの“Many Men”の
リミックスをちょっとやったんだよ
I just went high as f**k.
めちゃくちゃハイになって
I pressed upload.
アップしたら
Ni**as like, "What the f**k is that?"
みんな「なんだこれ？」って
But in reality,
でも実際のところ
I do feel like we different.
俺らは違うと思うんだ
It's certain things, for example, that like,
例えばある事とかって
なんていうか
you know, it's just like, it's just my shoes.
結局は俺の立場の
問題っていうか
You feel me?
わかる？
And I feel like 50 Cent just did certain things
50セントがやってきた事には
that I just probably wouldn't do in my life.
俺ならたぶん
一生やらない事もある
Like what?
例えば？
I think that 50 Cent is like the big, like, gangster image,
50セントってさ
デカいギャングのイメージっていうか
like, you feel me?
わかるだろ？
A role model of the rap career.
ラップのキャリアの
お手本みたいな存在で
And it's like almost even me, like, being a younger person,
俺ですらさ
若い頃は
I was, like, falling into it a little bit.
ちょっとそれにハマってた
Like, you know, I f**k with 50 too.
俺も50は好きだしさ
You feel me? Like, yeah, yeah.
わかる？
そう、そう
But then when I actually use my own two eyes and I'm like,
でも実際に自分の目で見て
思ったんだよ
all right, a lot of the s**t he do,
なるほどな
あいつのやる事の多くは
I feel like at his age, I would not be doing.
あの歳なら
俺はやってねぇなって
You know what I'm trying to say?
言いたいことわかる？
For me, a lot of the s**t he do, I would not do.
俺だったら
あいつのやる事の多くはやらない
Like you said, he too old for the trolling that he does.
言ってた通り
あの歳であの煽りはないって
Yeah, you feel me?
そう、わかる？
He got me in 25 years.
俺より25も上だぜ
I feel like he didn't even come down to this level and troll me right now.
今んとこ俺のレベルまで降りてきて
煽ってはこないけどな